DWAYNE BURROWS

Junior Software Developer

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I intend to graduate from Coder Academy with an aim to focus on gaining knowledge and experience. Preferable spending time in a working environment as a Junior Dev or an Intern.

CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

Secured an Internship with a company FitBox from the 6th of August continuing through until the 4th of September, Gaining real world experience from Experience Devs from web and mobile App development.

Polish Rugby Champion 2019
New Zealand Rugby ambassador XV 2019,2018,2017
New Zealand heartland XV
Nominated for New Zealand Heartland player of the year 2013
Inside Running Academy Scholarship Reciever 2012

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Javascript M.E.R.N stack Typescript React React Native Ruby on Rails CSS3 HTML5

Github

CONNECT WITH ME!

mobile: 0405 417 424 Burrows.Dwayne@icloud.com Morayfield, QLD, Australia github.com/dwaynediddy linkedin.com/in/dwaynediddy/

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

CODER ACADEMY

Diploma in Information Technology

- February 2020 August 2020
- Ruby- Terminal Application
- CSS3 & HTML5 Developer Portfolio
- Rails 2 way Marketplace Application
- Javascript M.E.R.N stack
- Typescript React Application Development
- Github Repository
- Agile S.C.R.U.M Practical and Theory

HARTPURY UNIVERSITY U.K

Sports and Business management

- 2017 - 2018 Foundation year

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTER JUNIOR DEVELOPER AUGUST 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Working With experienced Senior Developers.
- Working in an Agile Environment using S.C.R.U.M.
- Working on real world mobile Apps with React Native

CONTRACTED RUGBY PLAYER 2015-PRESENT

- Ogniwo Sopot R.F.C, Sopot, Poland Player, November 2018 2019
- ConeyHill R.F.C, Gloucestershire, England Payer/Coach, July 2017 2019
- Galashiels R.F.C, Galashiels, Scotland Player september 2015 2017

MACHINIST AT SOUTH ISLAND SEED DRESSING 2010-2015

- Operating forklift to safety standards
- Operating heavy duty machines for seed cleaning
- Inventory control
- Trained new staff in Tasmania